velvetblues.com 2013-06-30

# Privacy Policy – Velvet Blues Web Design

By browsing or using our Website, by providing us with information, or by downloading any material from the Website at http://www.velvetblues.com/, you are indicating your acceptance of the Privacy Policy below.

 **Overview**

Velvet Blues has created this Privacy Policy in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to helping our users better understand what information we collect about them and what may happen to that information. This privacy policy only applies to transactions and activities on the Website, but does not apply to any other website or offline point of contact between Velvet Blues and users. Please review this privacy policy periodically as we may modify it from time to time.

 **Non-Disclosure Agreement (NDA) for clients**

Velvet Blues respects your creative genius and professional artwork. We will only use your submitted materials to assist you with your projects and feature it in our portfolio. Your copyrights will always remain yours. We will not take your creative artwork for use on any other site, resell it, or give it to anyone under any circumstance.

Velvet Blues guarantees that all information shared with it will remain confidential.

Velvet Blues will never contact your clients or clients of your clients; we do respect your business and will not compete with you for it.

 **Information We Collect**

This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the Velvet Blues website. On some pages, you can order products, and make requests. The types of personal information collected at these pages are: (1) Email address, (2) Client informational requests, (3) Information concerned to orders (source files, client notes) and (4) Information on referring sites by using cookies and tracking your IP address.

 **How We Use Personal Information**

Our primary goal in collecting Personal information and Demographic Information is to provide you with a smooth, efficient, and customized experience. This allows us to provide services and features that most likely meet your needs and to customize our service to make your experience easier. Your Non-public Demographic information is kept confidential.

Please note that your personally identifiable information will be stored and processed on our hosting company’s servers in the United States. The laws on holding personal data in the United States may differ from laws in other countries but as we explain below, Velvet Blues will hold and transmit your information in a safe, confidential and secure environment.

We use your email address to help us efficiently operate the Website, to contact you in connection with your transactions and other activities on the Website (including, but not limited to, confirmation emails or important news that could affect your relationship with the Website. These types of communications are known as “Operational Communications.” In some cases, Operational Communications may also contain commercial messages, such as ads and special offers.

We also use personal information to send you newsletters, information, offers and other promotional materials for Velvet Blues’ or third parties’ goods or services. We attempt to send you offers that are of value to you, such as discounts, exclusive offers, or special event information. The Website provides you with options to decline to receive communications from VelvetBlues.com (other than those contained in Operational Communications).

To operate the Website, including processing your transactions and supporting your activities on the Website, we may share your personal information with our agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, email origination, receipt or support services, customer relationship management services, and order fulfillment. We require these entities not to use your information for any other purpose.

Any third party with whom we are allowed to share your personal information is authorized to use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Those who contact you will need to be instructed directly by you regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them.

 **Our Security Precautions**

Our website has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information that we collect online.

 **Notice of Change**

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. All changes to this policy are effective after we provide you with at least 30 days notice of changes by posting the changes to the Site. We provide you with 30 days notice to allow you the opportunity to notify Velvet Blues if you do not agree to such changes. After the 30 day period, Velvet Blues may use previously gathered information about you in ways consistent with the new Privacy Policy.

This statement was last revised on December 29, 2007.

If you have any questions or concerns regarding this privacy policy, the practices of the Website, or your dealings with the Website, please contact info@velvetblues.com
